# **Sharad Kumar Singh**

Student of Bundelkhand Institute of Engineering and Technology Jhansi



# **Contact**

#### **Address**

Noida Sector-31 Gautam Buddha Nagar, (U.P)

#### **Phone**

+91-9716805427

#### **Email**

Singhsharad529@gmail.com

### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ss529/

# **Skills**

| Core Java         |  |
|-------------------|--|
| C++ Programming   |  |
| Data Structure    |  |
| MySQL             |  |
| Microsoft Office  |  |
| HTML/CSS          |  |
| Python            |  |
| Digital Marketing |  |
| JAVASCRIPT        |  |
| Angular           |  |

# **Education**

# **Bachelor of Technology**

Bundelkhand Institute of Engineering and Technology Jhansi 2018 – Present | CGPA – 7.93

#### Intermediate

B.S Inter College Noida 2016 – 2018 | **Percentage – 87.6%** 

## High School

R.S.S Inter College Noida 2014 - 2016 | Percentage – 91.2 %

# Language

English (Intermediate) Hindi (Advance)

## **About**

An honors student with a record of academic and extracurricular success with extensive leadership experience. Adept at working across departments with faculty, administrators, and students. Keen interested in web developing, programming languages and other technologies.

# Experience

## **Digital Marketing Intern at**

Rising People Welfare society, Delhi | 07/2020 - 08/2020 |

Coordinator at

Student Council of Information and Technology

B.I.E.T Jhansi | 12/2019 - Present |

Coordinator at

Cultural Sub-Council, B.I.E.T Jhansi | 07/2019 - Present |

# Certifications

| Computer Networking: Coursera            | 06/2020 – 06/2020 |
|--|-------------------|
| Full Stack Web Development: Verzeo       | 05/2020 – 07/2020 |
| Digital Marketing: Google Digital Garage | 06/2020 – 06/2020 |
| Python: Udemy                            | 06/2020 – 06/2020 |
| Relational Database And SQL: Coursera    | 05/2020 – 05/2020 |
| Cloud Foundation: Great Learning         | 04/2020 - 05/2020 |
| Java Training: ICT Academy At IITK       | 06/2019 – 07/2019 |

# **Projects**

#### **Interior Design Website** | 07/2020 - 07/2020

A Home Interior Design Website using different technology like HTML, CSS, JQUERY, NODEJS etc. Project under Verzeo.

**Quake Tester** | 06/2020 - 06/2020

An earthquake tester window detects earthquake on a map by choosing (Hover effect) a particular area.

## Building a Text-Based Bank in Java | 05/2020 - 06/2020

A Database management system. In which we can manage data of a website. A grocery website where people purchase items and we have to manage all the details of customers as well as employees, like add/delete/update customers.

#### Prospect Encore analysis | 06/2019 - 07/2019

A software designed for a car showroom to manage a detailed database of it's customers and employees. (using JAVA, MYSQL).

Date: 20/11/2020 Place: Noida